{
    "subject": "resource/La_Robla",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "La Robla is located in Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9831315279006958,
            "question": "Is La Robla a city in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9220148324966431,
            "question": "Where is La Robla located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7752922773361206,
            "question": "Besides being in Spain, are there any other notable facts about La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.742431104183197,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the geographical location of La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7216225862503052,
            "question": "How would you describe the location of La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5949670076370239,
            "question": "What might someone find in or near La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5489133596420288,
            "question": "What country is home to La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5409606099128723,
            "question": "What is known about La Robla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38892874121665955,
            "question": "Is there anything specific La Robla is known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.303896963596344,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the people who live in La Robla?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=La Robla is located in Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5397_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything specific La Robla is known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5397_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about La Robla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5397_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country is home to La Robla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5397_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5397_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that La Robla is a municipality located in the province of Le\u00f3n, Castile and Le\u00f3n, Spain, which confirms that it is indeed located in Spain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that La Robla is located in Spain, specifically within the province of Le\u00f3n and the region of Castile and Le\u00f3n."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}